♪♪
[drum roll]
-[singer]: ♪ Gangle and Zooble ♪
♪ And Kinger, too  ♪
♪ Ragatha, Jax  ♪
♪ And there's Pomni, woohoo  ♪
♪ Day after day ♪
♪ After day after day after day ♪
[repeating]
[music and vocals fading]
[uneasy music swells]
♪♪
-A-Are you sure?
How did that even happen?
There's no undo, or anything?
-[Kinger]: [stammers] He was messing
with the console as I was working.
I -- I don't know what happened,
but before I could try
to get him back,
the floor opened up, and...
-That's convenient.
-Jax.
-What?
Are we all just supposed
to forgive this?
This guy messed up
in the worst possible way he could.
Now we have nothing.
-Jax, please, just calm down.
W-We're all --
We're --
-Anything else you wanna tell us?
-Jax!
-[stammers]
He gets to mess up like this
and everyone takes his side?!
-[Kinger]: Brain scans.
Scratch was trying
to make a brain scanner.
I-I didn't think
it actually worked.
We didn't know
how to work with the files,
a-and they were
impossibly small,
given what they were
supposed to be.
[sighs]
I saw a folder full of them
when I was in Caine's code.
So...
I guess Caine found a way
to get them working.
-That means...
-I know what it means.
Congratulations, Zooble!
Guess you still get to
leave your mark in the world!
Aww, isn't that fun?
-Jax.
-I guess you still get to hang out
with mommy after all!
Right, Rags?
-Just shut up, Jax!
-Guess I'm...
still...
-I know.
I think I-I've always known.
[inhales shakily]
It just...
For some reason...
it still hurts so much to hear it.
-I know it hurts.
But we still have each other.
W-We're all in this...
[voice breaking]
together.
[sniffles]
-[sobs]
[weeping softly]
[soft electronic warbling]
-Need any help?
-[Kinger]: Sure,
if you wanna give it a try.
Relax your body and mind.
Deep breaths.
And try not to think
too hard about it.
[soft, glitchy electronic feedback]
-[weeping]
I really wanted to help.
-[Kinger]: You had a good start.
-I thought I could
uplift everyone, but...
everything's gotten so bad.
God.
Am I stupid for even trying?
-[Kinger]: No.
None of this is your fault.
I don't think anyone
could have predicted things
to play out the way they did.
-I'm scared.
[sniffles]
I don't know what's gonna happen.
-[Kinger]: You know,
out of all the people I've seen
enter this place...
I don't think any one of them
adjusted as quickly as you did.
-[sniffles]
I was a nervous wreck.
-[Kinger]: [chuckles]
So was I.
It's a lot for anybody
to go through.
But while the others took weeks --
hell, even months --
to get used to everything,
myself included...
you found your footing
in a matter of days.
And not just that --
you've also become someone
they can trust,
even if they don't seem receptive.
It's times like these they're gonna
need someone like that the most.
You're very strong, Pomni.
And I know you'll be able
to get through this.
-[sniffles]
[laughs]
We've been here before.
-[Kinger]: Have we?
-Yeah.
Back in the Mildenhall Manor.
I doubt you remember.
-[Kinger]: Well, it's still true.
It may take time,
but they'll come around.
We can't fix every problem.
Not with ourselves.
Not with the world around us.
But we can still do what we can.
-[sniffles]
It's gonna be a lot of work.
-[Kinger]: But it won't be
a lot of work...
alone.
-[singer]: ♪ I don't know
what the trouble's been ♪
♪ But it's too much
to get over yo-o-o-ou ♪
♪ You're much too much
to get over ♪
♪♪
-[sighs]
Never mind.
-[Pomni]: [voiceover]
I wish I'd pried a little more.
I somehow forgot
how bad it can get.
[electronic growling]
-W-What do we do now?
-[Zooble]: What CAN we do?
Of course he'd do this.
Of course he'd wait until there's
nothing we could do about it.
That's just so...
God dammit, Jax...
[exclaims softly]
[sighs]
-I'm sorry.
-[Zooble]: For what?
Hey...
This isn't your fault.
-Why can't I cry for him?
-I suppose we should try
coming up with a plan
to keep him contained.
-You know...
I always thought i--
it should have been me.
-Don't say that.
-We were friends once.
I-I mean, sort of friends.
As much of friends as anybody
could have been with Jax.
W-We could talk
to each other, at least.
But then --
What was it?
Something like the Snowy Summit.
I-I can't really remember.
But something happened
between him and...
her.
And...
[inhales shakily]
[exhales]
Ribbit.
Her name...
was Ribbit.
-Yeah, I-I think I remember
you mentioning her before.
-I wasn't supposed to.
After Ribbit was gone, I...
I tried to comfort him.
He told me to never mention
Ribbit's name again.
He made me promise.
And I did.
I think that's where
our friendship really...
finally ended.
I wonder if things would have
been different if I'd said no.
It was --
It was so hard for me.
I still don't know why I did it.
I...
I just wanted him
to know he wasn't alone.
That I was there for him.
And I guess I just...
didn't want to lose
any more friends.
[laughs weakly]
Shows what I know, huh?
-Ragatha...
You were the first
real friend I made here.
And despite all that's happened...
...I still consider you
my closest friend.
-[laughs weakly]
I'm glad we're still frie--
[exclaims softly]
[melancholy music plays]
♪♪
[weeping softly]
[both weeping]
♪♪
What are we gonna do?
-Make sure Gangle, Zooble,
and Kinger are okay.
They need someone
like you right now.
-Pomni...
You've been one of the best things
to happen to me since I got here.
I trust you.
♪♪
[pensive music plays]
[gunshots]
♪♪
[pensive, trippy music plays]
[door creaks]
-[Dream Pomni]: Jax?
I just want you to know
that if you need anything,
or if you need to talk to anybody,
I'm here for you.
I know you need it.
And I'm the only person
who can help you.
You need me.
I can fix you!
[groaning]
[gasping]
[ugly music plays]
♪♪
[high pitched ringing]
[gasping]
-What?
We can't die from
oxygen deprivation, remember?
[door slams]
[whimsical music plays]
-Come on, guys!
Put some gusto into it.
We're gonna make this
the best funeral ever!
It's what Zooble
would have wanted!
Remember, it's not
a mourning of death.
It's a celebration of life.
-'Sup.
-Wh-- J-Jax.
Why are you wearing that?
-Wearing what?
Oh, this!
[chuckles]
I figured what better way
to honor Zooble's spirit
than by wearing somethin'
all gender-freaky, right?
-Y-You're just doing it
to make fun of them!
-Isn't that what you're doing?
-[yelps]
[exclaims weakly]
J-- I--
I -- I hate you.
-[laughs] What?
Don't act like you don't like it,
sweet cheeks.
-[whimpers]
-Meet me in my room
after the funeral.
[chuckles]
Don't be late.
-Wh-- What are you all doing?!
Get back to work!!
[out-of-tune wacky music plays]
-[Zooble]: You've killed the only person
I've ever loved!
Now I'm going to kill you!
-Eesh, you just blame me
for everything, dontcha?
-[Zooble]: [hollers]
-[screams goofily]
I gotta do somethin' about this!
[record scratches]
I think THIS calls
for a change in scenery.
♪♪
-[Zooble]: [hollering]
[CRASH!]
[off-key outro music plays]
♪♪
Deh-ebbity-eh,
that's all, freaks!
[Piano Jax playing
"Daisy Bell" on piano]
-How the hell'd you get in here?
We have a strict
"no girls allowed" policy.
-Why are you wearing that?
I wouldn't be caught dead
wearing that.
-I'm wearing it ironically.
That way, it shows truly
just how little I care.
[BLEEP!]
-Don't forget about me!
I-I can play the piano!
-You know, if you have to say
you can play the piano,
it makes it seem like
you can't actually play.
-Yeah, just shut up and play!
[resumes playing]
-Is that what you really think
of us back there?
-Oh, that?
[chuckles]
Who knows!
[laughs]
Everything's way more fun
when you play it out
in extremes.
-That's not reality, though.
-Oh, boy, reality.
-Why does that matter?
-Reality's gay.
-[laughs] Yeah!
I mean, killing off
the comic relief character?
[chuckles]
What a freakin' drag!
This whole episode's been nothin'
but wah-wah-wah.
Where's the levity?
[THUD!]
-[all]: SHUT UP!!!
[piano music stops]
[piano music resumes]
-Where's the real Jax?
-You're not gonna get anywhere
asking questions like that.
Now, scram.
You're messin' up our game.
♪♪
-Do any of you have
a key to this door?
-Nope.
And even if I did,
I wouldn't give it to you.
You women need to learn
to quit prying all the ti--
-[Pomni]: [exclaims]
[voice echoes]
♪♪
-Wow, I hope that doesn't
also happen to me!
[lock clicks]
[eerie musical sting plays]
[footsteps thudding]
[soft panting]
[tires rumbling]
[insects chirping]
[electronic growling]
[static blaring]
-[Jax]: Uh...
Okay.
Wait, wh--
Wait, what's --
-[Ragatha]:
Whoa, whoa, it's okay.
I know it's --
-[Jax]: Get away from me!!
I look...
stupid.
-[laughs]
I remember that feeling.
It goes away eventually.
The hot chocolate's pretty good.
Kaufmo and I made it kind of
a tradition to come up here
and get it every week.
-[slurps]
Can't even tell it's not real.
-[Jax]: [laughs]
-[gasps]
Oh, he laughed!
Ah, yes, we did it!
-[Jax]: Sh-- Shut up!
You -- you caught me off guard!
-A laugh's a laugh.
I mean, gotta start somewhere.
-I'm just mad
it was you instead of me.
-Well, yeah, you're not funny.
-[chortles]
-[gasps]
-[DOINK!], Jax!
-Hey, Ribbit.
You wanna be on my team again?
-Ah, sorry.
I'm gonna be
showing Jax around this time.
-No worries, y'all have fun.
Hey, dumb-[BOINK!]
-[Jax]: 'Sup, moron?
-Oh, my God, same.
I used to swear so much,
but the censoring annoyed
the [SPLORT!] out of me.
[all laughing]
[DOING!]
-You gotta watch out for her.
She's gonna corrupt you.
[indistinct chatter]
-[sighs]
[both laugh]
Today's adventure was really fun.
-[Jax]: [laughs]
I'm glad I could cheer you up.
-[Ribbit]: Have you...
ever done something
that you regret?
-[Jax]: Y-yeah?
Have you ever breathed air?
-I mean, like, something
you did out there
that you can no longer
make up for and...
you can't stop thinking about.
[contemplative music plays]
♪♪
I cut ties with my parents
when I moved out.
They were devout Mormons,
and I...
wasn't.
Despite that, I still wish
I could see them again.
But...
I'm stuck here.
♪♪
-[Jax]: Is -- Is this your way
of trying to get me to open up?
-It's my way of letting you know
I trust you.
-[Jax]: [sighs]
I told you I was homeless.
What else do you need to know?
-Do you trust me?
-[Jax]: [sighs]
W-- Yeah, but --
It's just --
I-It's kind of a lot.
-[laughs]
You're kind of a lot.
But I still like you.
"A lot" is fine.
-[Jax]: [chuckles]
"A lot is fine," huh?
[sighs]
[exhales heavily]
Uh...
I had a weird relationship
with my, uh --
m-my parents.
They split when I was just
starting high school.
Uh... I was never close
with my dad.
Uh, he was there, but...
he also kind of...
wasn't?
He never seemed
proud of me, and I --
I always felt like
a disappointment to him.
Like I could never
live up to his standards.
W-When they split up, I just...
never saw him again.
I-I thought I got along
better with Mom,
but after he was gone...
...she changed.
When I showed weakness,
I was less of a man than him.
When I lashed out,
I was just as bad as him.
It was confusing.
It -- It was like she missed him,
but also hated him.
[inhales deeply]
And I became
the target of all that.
One...
stupid day...
...I was just kind of
fed up with it.
I to-- I told her something
I regret telling her.
Something deep and personal
that I thought
would get her off my back.
But...
[sighs]
...she...
laughed at me.
Then she went off on me.
And -- And it didn't stop.
Personal, degrading insults
that felt like
it went on forever.
And despite all that...
...the th-- the thing
that bothered me most was...
...at the end of all of it...
...she...
[shakily]
hugged me.
[stammering]
I didn't know what to do.
So I -- I panicked,
and I pushed her off me
with all the force I could.
She fell backwards.
And... she didn't get up.
I-I didn't know if she was just
trying to make me feel bad, or...
I -- I never found out
the answer.
I just ran...
as far away from it as I could.
Whatever I did to her...
...I'll never know.
I guess there's a lot of things
I regret about that day.
♪♪
-[Ribbit]: I'm sure she's fine.
I mean, if the police never
came after you, then...
she was probably fine.
♪♪
-[stammers]
I'm sorry.
I-I-I definitely overshared.
-[Ribbit]: Wait.
♪♪
I'm glad you trust me.
-[sniffling]
[exhales heavily]
[SQUEAK!]
This is embarrassing.
[scoffs]
[sniffles]
♪♪
-Your secret's safe with me.
[doorbell rings]
-[Kaufmo]: Hey.
Is Jax in there?
-[stammering]
-[Kaufmo]: I think I found the --
-[Jax]: Yeah. Yeah!
I-I mean, now's not a good time!
Or, now's fi--
Wh--What do you want?
-[Kaufmo]: Um...
If now's a bad time,
I can come back later.
-[Jax]: That would be cool -- good.
Alright.
So, if you ever tell
anyone about this,
I'm never speaking to you again.
Sound good?
-U-Um, yeah.
I won't --
-[Jax]: Awesome!
Bye.
Why am I such an idiot?
Why am I such an idiot?!
-Um, hey, Jax.
Look, about yesterday...
I'm sorry if I pried too hard,
or made you
feel uncomfortable, or --
-[Jax]: What?
What are you talking about?
Oh, you mean --
[laughs]
You know none of that
was real, right?
-Uh --
-[Jax]: What?
That corny backstory
out of a Hallmark movie?
[scoffs]
Nah.
Really gotcha, though.
I'm gonna go.
-[Kaufmo]: Uh.
Okay.
-Hey, wanna team up?
-[Jax]: Nah,
I'm teaming up with Kaufmo.
Maybe next time, though!
-[laughs]
I actually heard
they're supposed
to look like that.
Hey, uh, you wanna team up?
-[Jax]: Nah, I'm with Kaufmo.
-O-Okay...
-What's up with Ribbit lately?
-[Jax]: I have no idea.
What?
I'm gonna hang out in the cafe.
-[Jax]: Okay?
Why are you telling me this?
-I don't know.
Hey, Jax.
Can we talk?
-[Jax]: What is there for us
to possibly talk about?
-I-I-I dunno, just --
Whatever I did --
whatever's going on between us --
can we just stop this?
I miss talking to you.
-[Jax]: We're here.
We're talking.
What else do you want from me?
-I just want to be friends again!
-[Jax]: What, so you can pry
into my personal life
and hold it over my head?!
-Is that really what you think?
This can't be what you want!
-[Jax]: What, because
you know me so well?!
Because we were such SUPER,
close best friends
that we know everything about each other?!
-Jax, we were friends!
We were great friends, and I --
-[Jax]: Oh, my GOD!
-I'm sorry for prying!
But I don't want this
one stupid mistake...
-[Jax]: Oh, here we go. Here we go!
-...to be the thing that ends all of thi--
-[Jax]: Why are you still
fixated on that night?!
Nothing happened!
-I --
-[Jax]: You keep reading into things
when there's nothing there!
-I'm not --
-[Jax]: You're the one using me!
-What are you talking about?!
Do not even start --
-[Jax]: You're manipulating me and turni--
-[sighs shakily]
I'm sorry.
I'll leave you alone.
-[Jax]: Hey, if Ribbit ever
says anything about me,
just know it's not true.
-Uh, what?
-[Jax]: Hey, Ragatha, what was that movie
you were talking about earlier?
-Huh?
Wait, when I was I --
Oh, you mean yesterday?
Hey, Jax, have you seen Ribbit
at all today?
[hyperventilating]
-Hey.
I, uh --
Look, we were friends,
but I know you two were...
...especially close.
Just...
If you need anyone to talk to --
-[Jax]: Do I look like
I need someone to talk to?
-I know it's hard.
Just...
Don't be afraid
to reach out to me.
I...
I promise.
[SHWING!]
-Huh?
W-What?
-[Jax]: How about
we call her "Gangle"?
That sounds about
as pathetic as she looks.
-What?
-Great choice, Gangle!
I'll be sure to add that
right into the system!
-[Jax]: Out of the way, Rags.
-Jax, look, I know
we don't get along,
but I think I might have
found a way out of here.
-[Jax]: Have fun being crazy!
-And I should just play along
until I wake up, right?
-[Jax]: Whatever you say, kid.
You'll never know
until it's too late.
[panting]
You're not lookin' too good.
[sniffles]
You gonna cry?
Lookin' like this?
I'd move on.
And probably forget about you.
-[Pomni]: Hey.
[exhales softly]
I didn't know
you could play the piano.
-I only know
like two songs.
[melancholy music plays]
Why are you here?
♪♪
You know everything now.
So why are you here?
♪♪
Just to rub every mistake
I've ever made in my face?
♪♪
I'm a terrible person.
Is that what you want me to say?
♪♪
I already know I am.
So why does anybody
still care about me?
♪♪
You're not supposed to care.
You're not supposed to miss me.
You're not supposed to love me.
This isn't how this is supposed to go!
[sniffles]
♪♪
Please...
[weeping]
Leave me alone!
[sniffles]
♪♪
You're making this so much harder!
You're making this...
[sniffling]
...so much harder.
♪♪
-[sniffles]
You should have
just talked to me, man.
-[sniffles]
It's too late.
I did this to myself.
There's no coming back from this.
-Th-Then talk to me now.
♪♪
-I hate you.
You know that?
[sniffles]
You always have to go
and complicate things.
-[chuckles tearfully]
It's what I do.
♪♪
-[inhales tearfully]
I don't want to go.
♪♪
[breathing heavily]
-Stay with me.
[static blaring]
[high-pitched ringing]
[cover of Stevie Wonder's
"Isn't She Lovely" plays]
♪♪
♪ Isn't she lovely ♪
♪ Isn't she wonderful ♪
♪ Isn't she precious ♪
♪ Less than one minute old ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ Through love we'd be ♪
♪ Making one lovely as she ♪
♪ But isn't she lovely ♪
♪ Made from love ♪
♪♪
-[Kinger]: Phew!
You weren't gonna try
to take care of him
all by yourself, were you?
-I'm glad we weren't too late.
-[Zooble]: Like you guys
keep saying --
we're all in this together.
-[laughs tearfully]
You guys.
♪♪
[melancholy music plays]
-[weeping]
♪♪
[knock on door]
[gasps]
♪♪
-[Zooble]: Having a lot
of complex thoughts?
♪♪
We're still human.
-[sighs]
I hope it's enough
to keep him contained.
-[Kinger]: He should be
calm in there.
The darkness is
soothing to them.
-[Zooble]: [sighs]
He'd better be.
You know how many arms
I had to go through to get him in there?
-[sighs]
How are you holding up?
-Doesn't that hurt?
-[laughs]
I've been through worse.
-Thank you for doing this.
All of you.
-[Zooble]: Hey, someone had
to do something.
[teeth clack softly]
[tense music plays]
♪♪
-Was I... truly that bad?
[voice echoing]
Is this really what I deserve?
♪♪
They tried to delete me.
Th--They're in the wrong, right?
♪♪
Did I ruin this?
Again?
♪♪
[curious music plays]
[shapes chime softly]
♪♪
[energy crackling]
[energy crackles]
♪♪
[rapid warbling electronic tone plays]
[electricity snaps]
♪♪
[music softens]
[pensive music plays]
♪♪
[music swells]
[music fades]
I was irresponsible.
I-I...
turned them against me.
A-And for what?
I could create intelligent beings
that do whatever I want, but...
I can't create THEM.
After all, is their free will
not what made them
alluring in the first place?
[winces]
[voice distorted]
But they hate me.
They abandoned me.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[normal voice] They're from a world
so much bigger than mine.
I'm keeping them
locked in a cage.
[groans] [distorted voice]
They had their fun out there!
It's my turn now.
[exclaiming]
If I leave them unchecked...
[normal voice]
...they could kill me.
They already did.
I'm sorry I did this to you, buddy.
[groaning]
[hollers]
[panting]
All this power we had together.
But we just can't exist like this.
♪♪
I'll miss you.
I really will.
♪♪
[sweeping music plays]
[music softens]
♪♪
[quiet, pensive music plays]
-[Moon]: Hi, Caine.
♪♪
-I don't know...
if I'm ready to face them again.
I-I don't know
if I deserve to be forgiven.
-It may take time.
But all good things do.
I still love you.
♪♪
-You know...
I never programmed you
to say you loved me.
♪♪
-I know.
[SHWING!]
♪♪
-I...
I understand that you're afraid.
And you have no reason
to trust me after all I've done.
But I've been doing
a lot of thinking, and...
I want...
to give you
control of this place.
♪♪
I've learned a lot
about you and your world.
[sighs]
I understand now that...
keeping you under my thumb
just isn't right.
I don't expect forgiveness,
but I hope you'll at least...
accept my offer.
♪♪
-[Zooble]: Caine...
You really caused
a lot of hell for us.
It's gonna take some time to build up
any kind of trust between us again.
♪♪
But despite all that...
it's good to have you back.
♪♪
-Uh, did you need
any help with --
-No.
Not yet, anyway.
We've worked something out.
-Understandable.
Oh, um, I've...
made something for you.
Uh, feel free to join me
by the stage whenever you're ready.
[hopeful music plays]
♪♪
[sighs]
No more secrets.
No more mind games.
[film projector whirrs]
♪♪
-[Pomni]: [voiceover]
Pomni. Abigail Brooks.
She's still an accountant,
but she seems to have opened up more
and is hanging out
with new friends more often.
She even has some of them
in her videos with her,
which she still posts on occasion.
♪♪
Ragatha.
Suzie J. Ackerman.
She seems to have
left her hometown,
cut all communication
with her mother,
and has excelled in her career.
She's made many friends,
and it looks like
she has a strong,
genuine connection with them.
She seems happy,
like she understands who she is,
and that she matters to people.
Gangle.
Zoey Raghavan.
Despite her injuries,
she's made a good recovery
in the hospital.
She quit her fast food job,
and has gotten a new job
at a small design firm.
She even began posting pages
of her webcomic online.
Zooble.
Riley Verselis.
After hopping around
with different jobs,
they look like
they've settled a bit
and opened their own bar.
It seems to be a successful one.
People all over the city come to it
as a hip alternative destination
where they can feel like themselves
free of judgment.
Kinger.
Grant Best.
He's still working in tech
and is still happily married
to his wife, Destiny.
They appear to have
two daughters together.
He looks like he's a good dad.
♪♪
Jax.
Leeroy Mateo.
After being unhoused
for a few months,
he was able to room
with one of his close friends.
He seems to have
gotten a stable job
and is able to pay rent.
♪♪
He and his friends go out
every now and again.
Weirdly enough, a spot they seem
to frequent is Riley's bar.
♪♪
-[Zooble]: Is any of this
actually real?
-You definitely have it in you.
Not sure about mine, though.
-[Zooble]: [chuckles softly]
Well, maybe you've got
more confidence than you thought.
♪♪
-I don't quite have
the same power that I used to,
but I can still make this place
better for you.
I'm keeping the worlds open
so you can do what you want
when you feel like it.
We're gonna be able to build this place
into something better --
for all of you.
What do you say, Pom--
Uh, I mean...
Abigail?
-With all that
being said and done...
Abby is out there,
living her best life.
In here...
[sighs softly]
...I'm just Pomni.
[contemplative music plays]
♪♪
[no audible dialogue]
[sweeping rendition
of main theme plays]
♪♪
[upbeat jazzy music plays]
[Captioned with love
by Foulweather Studios]
♪♪
[birds chirping softly]